officelovin.com 2019-09-25

# Privacy policy and cookies - Officelovin'

Menekuni permasalahan branding serta permasalahan harga jual tiap- tiap web serta game. Permasalahan branding pula wajib dapat dipelajari lebih lanjut supaya esoknya banyak yang terpikat pada game gambling [agen sbobet terpercaya](http://zona313.com/) taruhan online ini. Perihal ini hendak membagikan akibat lain semacam banyaknya era yang hendak berasosiasi ke dalam game sampai banyak orang yang turut mensupport game gambling duit asli dalam kompetisi yang terdapat.

Semacam metode intersepsi, metode mengutip ataupun membersihkan bola pula ialah metode yang bermanfaat buat bertahan dari serbuan yang dicoba rival. Tetapi, Kamu pula wajib berjaga- jaga kala [agen bola](http://qqibs.com/) melaksanakan metode ini, sebab dikira amat beresiko. Bila Kamu melaksanakannya dengan salah, Kamu bisa menyakiti rival Kamu serta Kamu dapat memperoleh kartu kuning dari penengah.

 **Effective date: May 10, 2018**

Welcome to Officelovin.com (Officelovin’). This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) is to help you understand what data Officelovin’ collects, and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information. This privacy policy informs you as to how you are protected under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) laws. This Privacy Policy governs the website and Officelovin’s other digital products and services.

 **Information We Collect**  
We collect information that you provide to us directly or automatically when you use the Services.

 **Information that you provide us or give us permission to obtain**  
When you register an account to use the Services, you voluntarily give us certain information. This information includes, but is not limited to: your name; gender; title; biographical information; username; and password. If you are creating a professional or brand account, we collect additional information including, but not limited to: your business name; business category; business description; business address; contact information; information about the size of the business. This information is used to create your profile on Officelovin’. You can customize some of the information displayed publicly in your Officelovin’ profile by going to your account and profile settings. If you provide us with profile information and you do not see a visibility setting, that information is public.

When you use the Services, you voluntarily provide us with additional information, including your recommendations, comments, replies to comments, users you are following, photos that you upload, collections of photos either that you or other users have uploaded, annotations on photos, photo collaborations, photo and story credits, and related data and content. You acknowledge and agree that the Services are for public consumption, including your photos, stories, and collections. By posting information using the Services, you agree to permit us to publicly disclose this material, as described in Officelovin’s Terms of Service.

If you make a purchase using the Services, you provide us with payment information, contact information and information on what you purchased. If you e-mail us, we may keep your message, e-mail address, and other contact information.

If you are using the Services on your mobile device, you can also choose to provide us with location data. You may also give us permission to access your information in other services. For example, you may link one or more of your social media accounts to the Services, which allows us to obtain information from those accounts (such as your friends or contacts). The information we get from those services depends on your settings or their privacy policies.

The Services may include social media features, such as the Facebook Like button, and widgets such as a “share” button, or other interactive features. These features may collect various personally identifiable information and cookies to enable the feature to work correctly. These features and widgets are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing them.

 **Information that we collect automatically when you use the Services**  
When you use the Services, data is created and recorded automatically. Some of the types of information that we collect are:

Log data. When you use the Services, our servers automatically record information (“Log Data”), including but not limited to information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. This log data may include your IP address, the address of the web pages you visited that had Officelovin’ features, browser type and settings, the date and time of your request, how you used the Services, and cookie data.  
Cookie data. Depending on how you are accessing the Services, we may use “cookies” (a small text file sent by your computer each time you visit our Services, unique to your Officelovin account or your browser) or similar technologies to record Log Data. When we use cookies, we may use “session” cookies (that last until you close your browser) or “persistent” cookies (that last until you or your browser delete them). You can set your browser to refuse to accept cookies. However, if you choose to refuse cookies, some features of the Services may not function properly.  
Device information. In addition to Log Data, we may also collect information about the device on which you are using the Services, including what type of device it is, what operating system you are using, device settings, unique device identifiers, your geolocation, and crash data. Whether we collect some or all of this information often depends on what type of device you are using and its settings.  
Do Not Track. Your browser may support a “Do Not Track” option that can be selected in your browser settings, which sends a signal to websites you visit informing them that you do not want certain information about your visit to be collected. At this time we do not respond to browser “Do Not Track” signals, as we await the work of interested stakeholders and others to develop standards for how such signals should be interpreted.  
Analytics and Usage. We use data analytics and work with certain third party service providers to help us understand and improve the use of our Services. These third party service providers may collect information sent by your device as part of a web page request, such as cookies or your IP address. Third party ad partners may also share information with us to help us measure and tailor ads.  
Google Analytics. We use Google Analytics, which collects anonymous data for us to better serve you with both better website design and content.  
**What Google Analytics features do we use?**

Please see the feature list for Google Analytics at http://www.google.com/analytics/features.  
**What do we do with your data?**

All tracking information is used to help better design our content and web design to meet the needs of the customer and enhance the Service. All of our activity meets Google Analytics Terms of Service which can be found here. http://www.google.com/analytics/terms.  
Opt out of Google Analytics: You can opt out of the anonymous data collected from Google Analytics by disabling cookies in your web browser for the Services. This will only block Google Analytics Data for us, and will not affect other websites. You can also opt out of all Google Analytics Tracking Data on the web by installing a browser plugin provided by Google. This can be found here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout. The anonymous statistics we gather may be shared with a third party vendor to assist us with analyzing data, creating ads and web design. For more information about how Google uses data, visit http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners.

 **We use cookies from these companies**

  * Google LLC (Google Analytics);
  * Facebook Ireland Ltd. (online marketing platform, Facebook comments);
  * Twitter Inc.
  * LinkedIn Corporation
  * Pinterest Inc.

 **How We Use Your Information**  
We use the information we collect to improve the Services. We also use the information we collect to offer you customized content, for example, based on your preferences and content you post, to tailor the ads that we show you to your interests and to contact you for marketing purposes. We also use the information that we collect to notify you about updates to the Services, monitor and test the Services, and remember your login information so that you do not need to re-enter this information.

 **When We Share Your Information**  
We may share your information with third parties from time to time, including but not limited to:

Agents, Contractors, and Service Providers. We may share your information with our agents, contractors, or other service providers as needed to carry out the performance and functionality of the Services, fulfill your requests for authorized transactions, or provide user support.  
Analytics and Usage. We may share user information in the aggregate with third parties, such as advertisers and other businesses. For example, we may disclose to a business the number of users that have viewed their product or may disclose to a professional how many times their profile has been viewed.  
Third Party Ad Networks. We may use third party advertising companies to place advertisements on the Services or assist us in evaluating the effectiveness of our advertising, in accordance with applicable law. These companies may use cookies, web beacons, or other tracking technology to collect information (not including your name, address, or telephone number) about your visit to the Services and other sites and services in order to provide you with targeted advertisements. If you would like to learn more about behavioral advertising or to opt out of having this information used by companies that are part of the Network Advertising Initiative and the Digital Advertising Alliance to deliver targeted ads, please visit http://www.networkadvertising.org, http://www.aboutads.info/choices (DAA) and in Europe http://www.youronlinechoices.com.  
Affiliated Entities. We may share information from or about you with subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under common control with Officelovin, in which case, we require them to honor this Privacy Policy.  
Business Transfers. If we are acquired by or merged with another entity (or during the due diligence period of any such acquisition or merger), if substantially all of our assets are transferred to another company, or as part of a bankruptcy proceeding, we may transfer the information we have collected about you to the acquiring company.  
Other Users. Information that you post publicly through the Services (for example, photos, comments, or profile information) will be made publicly available.  
Investigations. We may investigate and disclose information from or about you, as permitted by applicable law, if we have a good faith belief that such investigation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process and law enforcement instructions and orders, such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, judicial proceeding, or other legal process served on us, helpful to prevent, investigate, or identify possible wrongdoing in connection with the Services, or helpful to protect our rights, reputation, property, or that of our users, subsidiaries, or the public.  
**Accessing and Modifying Your Information**  
If you are a registered user of the Services, we provide you with account settings and tools to access, correct, delete, or modify the personal information you have provided to us and associated with your account.

You can also permanently delete your account at any time by going to your account settings.

Search engines and other third parties may still retain copies of your public information, like your user profile and content you provide, even after you have deleted this information or deactivated your account.

 **Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time, and if we do we’ll post any changes on this page. If you continue to use the Services after those changes are in effect, you agree to the revised Privacy Policy. If the changes are significant, we may provide more prominent notice or get your consent as required by law.

 **Contacting Us**  
If you have any requests concerning your personal information or other inquiries regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us by e-mail at [michael@officelovin.com](mailto:michael@officelovin.com).
